(Sheldon:)of quantum mechanics?
(Howard:)Since every interpretation gives
exactly the same answer
(Howard:)to every measurement,
they are all equally correct.
(Howard:)However, I know you believe in
the Many Worlds Interpretation,
(Howard:)so I'll say that. Now do you
think I'm smart enough?
(chuckles):
No.
(Howard:)Oh, come on.
You might've gone to school
(Howard:)for a couple more years than me,
but guess what--
(Howard:)engineers are just
as smart as physicists.
(gasps)
You take that back!
(mimicking Sheldon):
No.
(Amy:)So, after drinks
with Bernadette,
(Amy:)I get home, and Penny calls
to complain about her.
(Amy:)And then while
I'm talking to Penny,
(Amy:)I get a text from Bernadette.
Wh... I'm trying to prepare
my lesson plan for Howard.
(Sheldon:)Why are you
telling me this?
(Amy:)Because it's taken 15 years, but
high school is finally awesome!
(Amy:)I love them both,
but I'm in the center now,
and I love that even more.